
export const quizQuestions_4 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does a ternary operator in JavaScript do?',
      choices: ['Defines a function with three parameters', 'Performs a three-way comparison', 'Shortens an if-else statement to a single line', 'Calculates the remainder of a division by three'],
      correctAnswer: 'Shortens an if-else statement to a single line',
    },
    {
      question: 'How is short-circuiting used in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['To create concise if-else statements', 'To optimize code execution by skipping unnecessary evaluations', 'To truncate long variable names', 'To reduce the size of the source code'],
      correctAnswer: 'To optimize code execution by skipping unnecessary evaluations',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the result of the expression: true && false?',
      choices: ['true', 'false', 'null', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: 'false',
    },
    {
      question: 'When using the OR operator (||), what value is returned if the first operand is truthy?',
      choices: ['The first operand', 'The second operand', 'true', 'false'],
      correctAnswer: 'The first operand',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can you use a ternary operator to assign a value to a variable based on a condition?',
      choices: ['By using the if keyword', 'By using the else keyword', 'By using a combination of ? and :', 'By using the switch statement'],
      correctAnswer: 'By using a combination of ? and :',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the nullish coalescing operator (??) in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['To concatenate two strings', 'To check for null or undefined values and provide a default value', 'To perform bitwise operations', 'To compare two objects for equality'],
      correctAnswer: 'To check for null or undefined values and provide a default value',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the result of the expression: false || true?',
      choices: ['true', 'false', 'null', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: 'true',
    },
    {
      question: 'In a ternary operator, what comes after the ? symbol?',
      choices: ['The condition', 'The true branch', 'The false branch', 'A colon (:)'],
      correctAnswer: 'The true branch',
    },
    {
      question: 'How does short-circuiting help improve performance in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['By reducing the overall file size', 'By skipping unnecessary evaluations in logical expressions', 'By compressing images in the project', 'By optimizing network requests'],
      correctAnswer: 'By skipping unnecessary evaluations in logical expressions',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which operator can be used for concise conditional rendering in React?',
      choices: ['if-else operator', 'Conditional (ternary) operator', 'Logical AND operator', 'Bitwise OR operator'],
      correctAnswer: 'Conditional (ternary) operator',
    },
  ],
}